Donohue, William Collection of International Longshoremen's Association Local 1286 Papers 6308
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
William Donohue Collection of International Longshoremen's Association Local 1286 Papers
1942-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Donohue, William
Archer-Daniels-Midland Company
Dellwood Elevator
6308
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers.
7130243
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5078: New York Shipping Association and the International Longshoremen's Association Records 5116: International Longshoremen's Association, United Marine Division, Local 333 and Quality Transportation Corp. et.al. Records 5261: International Longshoremen's Association New York District Council Records 5317: Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast and the ILWU Records 5559: International Longshoremen's Association Dock Strike Clippings
Collective labor agreements; Grievance procedures; Donohue, William J.; Archer Daniels Midland Company; Dellwood Elevator; International Longshoremen's Association; International Longshoremen's Association. Local 1286
7130243
- Instructions for Grain Elevator Stewards, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  November 10, 1943
- Archer-Daniels-Midland Company. Employee Bulletin, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  December 24, 1959. To All Salaried Employees
- Archer-Daniels-Midland Company. Maintenance Apprenticeship Standards (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Central Elevator Daily Bin Report, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1944-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dellwood Elevator Employee Rosters, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dues Books, 1967-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Analysis: Employers' Recourse When Union Contract is Violated, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Grievance Form. E. J. Leavy, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Union Requests (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Notice of Special Meeting, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Pension Plan, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Proposals Submitted to Management for Discussion, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Sanitation Inspection and Recommendations: Dellwood Elevator, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  May 7-8, 1959.
- The Scab Leader. Poem (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Supervisors' Conferences, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Employee Records, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)